It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
What's your name?
お名前は?
What was that?
何でしたっけ?
This is Senna.
セナです
Sena-chan, it's been a while.
セナちゃん、お久しぶり
I'm in uniform today.
今日は制服なんだ
That's right, today.
そうなんですよ、今日は
During your student days?
学生時代の?
Well, that's true.
まあそうだよね
Please stand up for a moment and show me.
ちょっと立って見せて
Wow, it suits you.
すごい、似合って
How old are you now?
今何歳だっけ?
Right now, I haven't even written down my birthday yet, so I'm 18 years old.
今は、まだ誕生日も書いてないから18歳
18 years old?
18歳?
How long will uniforms last?
制服はいつまで?
制服いつまで?
March 5th.
3月の5日
So it's still fresh.
じゃあまだ新鮮だね
I'd say it's fresh, or until recently.
新鮮って言うか、最近まで
TRUE?
本当?
Is it strange that this is fresh?
これ新鮮は変か?
I wore it until recently.
最近まで着てた
It was perfect.
ピチピチでした
Pichi Pichi?
ピチピチ?
It was perfect.
ピチピチでした
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
You can sit down.
座っていいよ
It's amazing, I feel like I'm being worshiped a little bit.
すごいね、ちょっと拝督感がある
Do you have a sense of worship?
拝督感ある?
Yeah.
うん
Can I have a chat?
チーしていい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I think it's a little early to take off your uniform.
制服を脱がすのは、ちょっと早いと思うからさ
Yeah.
うん
Can you blame me first?
先に、俺のこと責めてもらっていいかな?
nice.
いいね
Don't blame me, see you later.
こっちから責めんな、また後で
bed
ベッド
go?
行 く?
Shall we go to bed?
ベッド行く?
Yeah.
うん
Can you blame me a little more?
もう ちょっと責めてもらっていいかな?
A little more?
もうちょっと?
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Do you get nervous if you see something like that?
やだれとかあったら焦ったりする?
Yadare?
やだれ?
Where?
どこに?
Chikubi or something.
チクビとか
Chikubi?
チクビ?
Can you do it?
できるかな?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
I'm already embarrassed.
もう恥ずかしいよ
My love doesn't come out.
大好きが出てこない
Well then, lick it a lot.
じゃあ、たくさん舐めて
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
It's too hard, isn't it?
固いすぎでしょ
Because I want you to lick me more.
もっと舐めてほしいから
I want to put it on soon, but you're still wearing underwear, right?
そろそろ入れたいんだけど、 まだ下着履いてるよね?
Yeah.
うん
What's under the uniform?
制服の下、どんなの?
Get on your knees for a moment.
ちょっと膝立ちして
Kneel.
膝立ち
Shall I try wrapping the skirt?
スカートを巻くってみようか
Do you roll it?
巻くの?
Roll it up.
巻くって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
shame
恥
That's embarrassing.
ず かしい
Isn't it a little cool?
ちょっとかっこよくない?
underwear.
下着
I'll take a little time today.
今日はちょっと間にかけてだから
Last time, I wore white, fairly normal pants.
前回は白い、 割と普通なパンツだったけど
We talked for a little while.
ちょっとだけしゃべってみた
What about your butt?
お尻は?
My butt isn't normal.
お尻は普通じゃない
Isn't that normal?
普通じゃない?
Normal suits me though.
普通が似合ってるけどさ
I went to the trouble of asking her to wear some nice underwear, but...
せっかくいい下着履いてきてもらったんだけど、
May I ask you to take it off?
脱いでもらっていいかな
Just underwear?
下着だけ?
Do you wear underwear?
下着するの?
underwear.
下着
Should I wear underwear?
下着しようか
Do you wear underwear?
下着する?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Wrap your skirt?
スカート巻く?
huge.
でっかい
open.
開ける
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Stop it.
やめて
Would you like to?
しますか
What about rubber?
ゴムは?
Also?
また?
I didn't do it last time.
前回しなかったし
It's Nasaga, isn't it?
なさがでしょ
Did you quit?
や めた?
I want you to lick me again.
もう一回舐めてほしい
It doesn't change once or twice.
一 回も二回も変わらない
Can you do it while having shisha hair?
シシャの髪持ちながらできるかな?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's still tough.
相変わらずきっついよね
It feels amazing.
すごい感じ
Why don't you say anything?
何しようこと言わない?
difficult?
難しい?
difficult.
難しい
It's also difficult in my eyes.
目の中も難しくて
Yeah.
ええよ
Are you getting tired?
疲れてきた?
be careful.
気をつけて
Do the opposite.
反対をやって
Okay.
いいよ
Yo
よ
Yes.
い しょ
Your butt is so erotic.
お尻エロいよ
Are you going to put a difficult face on this?
難しい顔をこれ入れるの?
what?
何?
why?
なんで?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Let's do our best.
頑張ろう
slowly.
ゆっくり
Her ass is erotic.
お尻エロい
Erotic.
エロい
Are you tired?
疲れちゃったかな?
Shall we change?
変わろうか
Shall we go back?
バックしようか
back?
バック?
Okay.
いいよ
Take a look here.
ちょっとこっち見て
Just chew.
噛むだけ
Because I want to cum inside.
中に出したいから
Full of uniforms.
いっぱい制服のぼっか
Do you take pictures anywhere?
どこも撮るの?
Because it's erotic.
エロいから
It's true, isn't it?
まさらでしょ
I'm already having sex.
もうエッチしてるんだよ
The bra is also really cool.
ブラジャーもすごいかっこいい
So cool.
すごいかっこいい
cool?
かっこいい?
TRUE?
本当?
Let's take a picture.
撮っちゃおう
Well then, let's scratch it.
じゃあ、 手掻きしようか
Together in the future.
先々一緒に
A decided back love.
決まるバックラブ
Don't take pictures.
写さないで
It's roughly in the picture.
だいたい写って
It just came out a little.
ちょっとだけ出ちゃった
It only comes out a little.
ちょっとだけしか出てない
Because it only comes out a little.
ちょっとしか出てないから
still?
まだ?
Gome
ごめ
Hmm.
ん ね
It was empty inside.
中は空いたもんって
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね
Sorry.
ごめんね
It was so overflowing.
すごい溢れちゃった
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I have to do it properly later.
後でしっかりやらないと
Can you clean it?
お掃除できる?
Yeah.
うん
how was it?
どうだった?
Let's go cosplay.
コスプレいっちゃおう
It might have been my first time.
初めてしたかも
It's my first time.
初めてだね
Almost active.
ほぼ現役の
Is it still time?
まだ間に合う?
Totally on time.
全然間に合う
Should I scratch too much?
掻きすぎちゃおう?
So, is it Opride?
じゃあ、 オプライドか
Please be strong.
力払ってね
Also, it's naughty again.
また、 またエッチじゃね
bye bye.
バイバイ